<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Grants on Radiomics</title><link>/research/</link><description>Recent content in Grants on Radiomics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PRECIMET</title><link>/research/precimet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/research/precimet/</guid><description>PRECIMET is a multicentric prospective imaging trial currently ongoing at Vall d’Hebron University Hospital, Fundació Puigvert, Bellvitge Univerity Hospital, Malaga University Hospital, Santiago de Compostela University Hospital and Hospital Clínic de Barcelona.
Project summary This study follows Dr Perez-Lopez’s research line in diffusion MRI and stems from the need of a better imaging protocol to evaluate metastatic bone disease in clinical practice. Unlike the current standard-of-care techniques, MRI is non-invasive and offers anatomical and functional imaging that makes it a superior choice for both visceral and bone disease follow-up.</description></item><item><title>PREdICT</title><link>/research/predict/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/research/predict/</guid><description>PREdICT is a prospective imaging trial at the Vall d’Hebron University Hospital and the University Clinic at Navarra.
Project summary In this imaging study, initiated by Dr Perez-Lopez, we perform a prospective non-randomized multi-center study in patients treated with immunotherapy to clinically validate the CT-radiomics signature developed earlier by our group. Moreover, by acquiring multiparametric and functional MR and gathering biologically-relevant data from biopsies and blood samples, we can further develop a novel non-invasive imaging strategy for assessing solid tumors biology, immune cell activation and dynamics of response to immunotherapy based on radiomics signatures.</description></item><item><title>IseeMORE</title><link>/research/iseemore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/research/iseemore/</guid><description>IseeMORE research project is focused on unravelling tumor heterogeneity and integrating multi-omics data.
Project summary In this project, we propose to develop a novel multi-omics signature by incorporating the radiomics data from clinical images (multiparametric and functional MRI) allowing to characterize the intra-tumor heterogeneity in whole tumor volume and to monitor changes at different timepoints during the treatment. Our unique imaging protocol was implemented in a prospective clinical trial and allows to noninvasively quantify histological tumor characteristics such as cellularity, vasculature and hypoxia to better characterize which patients are more prompt to respond to ICIs.</description></item></channel></rss>