<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Team on Radiomics</title><link>/team/</link><description>Recent content in Team on Radiomics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Raquel Perez-Lopez</title><link>/team/raquel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/raquel/</guid><description>Raquel Perez-Lopez is the team leader of the Radiomics Group at VHIO, and consultant Radiologist at Vall d&amp;rsquo;Hebron Hospital, within the Vall d&amp;rsquo;Hebron Barcelona Hospital Campus. Her work aims to develop novel non-invasive imaging biomarkers in oncology to improve cancer patient care.
Scientific trajectory Dr Raquel Perez-Lopez is an experienced academic radiologist trained at Bellvitge University Hospital in Barcelona (Spain) and the Royal Marsden Hospital and the Institute of Cancer Research in London (UK).</description></item><item><title>Francesco Grussu</title><link>/team/francesco/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/francesco/</guid><description>Francesco joined VHIO in 2020. His research aims to develop novel Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) techniques for cancer assessment that are informed by histology. He is also involved in designing MRI acquisition and analysis pipelines in the clinical studies of the Radiomics Group.
Scientific trajectory Francesco is a biomedical engineer specialised in computational MRI, with almost 12 years of experience in MRI research. He graduated from the University of Cagliari (BEng Biomedical engineering, 2009) and University of Genoa (MEng Bioengineering, 2012), Italy.</description></item><item><title>Kinga Bernatowicz</title><link>/team/kinga/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/kinga/</guid><description>Driven by scientific curiosity, Kinga has gained a broad range of expertise in engineering, medical physics and environmental science. She joined VHIO in November 2019 and has focused on investigating tumor heterogeneity and integrating multi-omics data in predictive models for immunotherapy. Scientific trajectory Her academic journey started at Gdańsk University of Technology, where she obtained an engineering degree (B.Sc. in Environmental Protection and Management). She had always been interested in physics and soon after received her M.</description></item><item><title>Alonso Garcia-Ruiz</title><link>/team/alonso/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/alonso/</guid><description>Alonso is a biomedical engineer and has been member of the Radiomics team since 2018. He is currently pursuing his PhD, working on whole-body diffusion MRI as a biomarker of bone metastases, and on brain perfusion MRI for tumour characterization. Scientific trajectory In 2014, he obtained his B.Sc. at Universidad Carlos III de Madrid and his M.Sc. at Katholieke Universiteit Leuven in 2017, focusing on image processing, but also glancing at medical image acquisition, computer vision and machine learning within the healthcare context.</description></item><item><title>Óscar Llorián-Salvador</title><link>/team/oscar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/oscar/</guid><description>Óscar joined VHIO’s Radiomics team in late 2024 as a postdoctoral researcher. His research is focused on leveraging large language models (LLMs) to extract and process information from clinical patient reports and integrate them into multimodal models that also combine CT imaging for patient-tailored prognostic assessments. Scientific trajectory In 2014, Óscar obtained his B.Sc. in Biotechnology from the University of Oviedo, where he developed an interest in bioinformatics. He pursued that interest and in 2017 finished his M.</description></item><item><title>Olivia Prior Palomares</title><link>/team/olivia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/olivia/</guid><description>Olivia is a biomedical engineer who joined VHIO in 2021. Her research is focused on new imaging biomarkers identification and intratumor/microenvironment heterogeneity exploration. Scientific trajectory Olivia obtained a BS. in Biomedical Engineering from Universitat de Barcelona (2018). As part of her final degree project, she worked at the International Centre for Numeric Methods at Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya under the supervision of Dr. Eduardo Soudah, where she contributed to the development of an augmented reality system for oncological surgeries.</description></item><item><title>Caterina Tozzi</title><link>/team/caterina/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/caterina/</guid><description>After receiving a doctorate in applied mathematics, Caterina joined the Radiomics group in 2022. So far, her work based on mathematical and computational modelling in the study of biomedical systems. Now her research aims to integrate advanced imaging analysis with 3D molecular characterization.
Contact and links Email Github LinkedIn</description></item><item><title>Marta Ligero</title><link>/team/marta/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/marta/</guid><description>Marta is a biomedical engineer who joined the Radiomics group in 2018. She&amp;rsquo;s focused on the implementation of artificial intelligence for developing CT-based radiomics biomarkers of response to immunotherapy. She also has research interest in radiomics variability and biological translation.
Scientific trajectory Marta is a PhD student with expertise in artificial intelligence algorithms for medical imaging applications, especially on CT-based radiomics for predicting response to treatment. Marta graduated in Biomedical Engineering (2017) from the University of Barcelona (UB) and received her M.</description></item><item><title>Carlos Macarro</title><link>/team/carlos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/carlos/</guid><description>Carlos is a biomedical engineer who joined the Radiomics group in 2022. His research is focused on advanced Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) processing and multi modal analysis to identify new imaging biomarkers in oncology. Scientific trajectory Carlos obtained a BS. in Biomedical Engineering from Universidad de Sevilla (2021). As part of his bachelor&amp;rsquo;s thesis, he contributed to the development of a clinical prototype for pre-treatment verification of SBRT 4D in tumors subjected to respiratory movement, at Dr.</description></item><item><title>Maria Balaguer-Montero</title><link>/team/maria/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/maria/</guid><description>Maria is a biomedical engineer who joined the Radiomics group in 2021. Her research is focused on the development of automatic segmentation tools that can help for volumetric disease assessment. Scientific trajectory Maria obtained a BSc in Biomedical Engineering from Universitat de Barcelona (2022). As part of her Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Thesis, she entered the Radiomics Group, where she help develop a PET-CT-based radiomics signature to predict response in patients with non-Hodgkin&amp;rsquo;s Lymphoma treated with CART T-cells.</description></item><item><title> Ella Fokkinga</title><link>/team/ella/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/ella/</guid><description>Ella is a Biomedical Engineering student at the Delft University of Technology. She has joined the Radiomics group in September 2022, to do her master thesis here. In 2019, she obtained a BSc in Clinical Technology, also at TU Delft. The focus of her thesis is on estimating histological properties of tumours, based on diffusion MRI data. Specifically, she will develop an AI-based method to directly predict quantitative measures, such as cell size and intracellular fractions, from the raw MRI data.</description></item><item><title>Bente Gielen</title><link>/team/bente/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/bente/</guid><description>Bente joined the Radiomics Group in September 2022 for her master thesis. She studies biomedical engineering at the technical university of Delft, the Netherlands. Bente obtained a BS. in Biomedical Physics and Technology from Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam. (2019). Her thesis at VHIO will be focused on CT imaging for predicting response to immunotherapy. We will aim to develop a tool for more accurate response evaluation to Immune Checkpoint Inhibtors.
Contact and links Email</description></item><item><title>Daniel Navarro García</title><link>/team/daniel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/daniel/</guid><description>Daniel joined the group in November 2023 after finishing an MSc in bioinformatics at Vrije University of Amsterdam and being intern for one year at The Netherlands Cancer Institue. His main project involves the integration of multimodal data for the prediction of immunotherapy response using deep learning. He is also involved in other projects such as the use of Federated Learning for inter-institutional collaborative healthcare.
Academic Formation 2017 - 2021 BSc Biomedical engineering, Universidad Carlos III de Madrid</description></item><item><title>Marta Buetas</title><link>/team/martab/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/martab/</guid><description>Marta is a physicist with an MSc in Data Science who joined the Radiomics group in December 2024. Her main project involves the integration of multimodal data for the development of non-invasive imaging biomarkers for predicting response to different treatment mechanisms in metastatic colorectal cancer patients.</description></item><item><title>Athanasios Grigoriou</title><link>/team/thanos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/thanos/</guid><description>Athanasios is a mechanical engineer with a focus in computational methods that joined the Radiomics group in the Fall of 2022 as a PhD candidate. His research is focused on computational MRI methods coupled with artificial intelligence with the aim of earlier cancer detection, treatment personalisation and disease activity monitoring.
Contact and links Email</description></item><item><title>Andreu Antolin</title><link>/team/andreu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/andreu/</guid><description>Andreu is a radiology resident at Hospital Vall d&amp;rsquo;Hebron (Barcelona). He joined the Radiomics group in mid-2021 and gives support to the team in specific tasks such as image interpretation, labeling and radiomics-based model development. He is interested in the application of AI in the field of Radiology using Machine Learning and Deep Learning methods.</description></item><item><title>Anna Voronova</title><link>/team/anna/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/anna/</guid><description>Anna Voronova is a biomedical engineer that joined the Radiomics group at VHIO in 2022. Anna&amp;rsquo;s research centers on Artificial Intelligence and computational dMRI methods for application in earlier metastasis detection and tumour microenvironment characterisation for treatment evaluation.
Contact and links Email</description></item><item><title>Humaira Abdul Ghafoor</title><link>/team/humaira/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/humaira/</guid><description>Humaira joined the Radiomics group in March 2023. Her research is focused on biomedical imaging. She has studied software engineering, specialising in Machine learning.</description></item><item><title>Arnau Farré Melero</title><link>/team/arnau/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/arnau/</guid><description>Arnau is a physicist and a biomedical engineering student who joined the Radiomics group in 2022. He is focusing his curricular internship on developing a CT-based radiomics signature for the classification of colorectal cancer patients and injuries, framed in the COLOSSUS project.</description></item><item><title>Iker Zubieta</title><link>/team/iker/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/iker/</guid><description>Iker is a mathematician who joined the Radiomics group in 2022. He is focused on studying tumor heterogeneity. Iker obtained a BS. in Mathematics from Universidad del País Vasco/ Euskal Herriko Unibertsitatea. Iker is currently studying a Master in Statistics and Operations Research (MESIO) from Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya and will be carrying out his master thesis at the Radiomics group thanks to a BBVA Foundation Fellowship.
Contact and links Email LinkedIn</description></item><item><title>Júlia Ibañez Massa</title><link>/team/julia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/julia/</guid><description>Júlia is a biomedical engineering student who joined the Radiomics group in 2022. She was granted with a BBVA Summer Internship to develop a CT-based signature to classify colorectal cancer patients into further subtypes in the framework of the EU-funded COLOSSUS project.</description></item><item><title>Adrià Marcos</title><link>/team/adria/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/adria/</guid><description>Adrià joined the Radiomics group in 2023 after finishing his studies in Physics Engineering and Data Science Engineering in the UPC CFIS double engineering program. His current field of research is the usage of Federated Learning for inter-institutional collaborative healthcare+AI projects and the usage of Self Supervised Learning for image encoding.</description></item><item><title>Christina Zatse</title><link>/team/christina/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/christina/</guid><description>Christina joined the Radiomics group on February 2023 as a Data Curator. She has studied Physics in Athens, specializing in Nuclear and Particle Physics and completed her Master in Computational Biomedical Engineering at UPF in Barcelona. Her addition to the team is mainly to organize and maintain the databases for different projects and contribute to the integration of multi-omics data.</description></item><item><title>Camilo Monreal</title><link>/team/camilo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/camilo/</guid><description>Camilo is a Computer Scientist with a Master in Logic and AI who joined the Radiomics group in 2021. One of his main roles in the group is to provide support in the group’s computational cluster while enabling the development and implementation of final end-user applications.</description></item><item><title>Nikolaos Staikoglou</title><link>/team/niko/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/niko/</guid><description>Nikolaos (Nikos) is a Medical Doctor with training in Radiology. His research in VHIO is focused on identifying CT radiomics signatures in patients with Hepatocellular Carcinoma, treated with immunotherapy agents. Nikos (he/him) obtained his medical degree from Aristotle University of Thessaloniki, GR (2017) and continued his four–year training in Diagnostic &amp;amp; Interventional Radiology at AHEPA University Hospital of Thessaloniki (2018-2021). He holds a MSc in Biomedical Imaging from Maastricht University, NL (2022), with a special interest in radiomics and advanced neuroimaging.</description></item><item><title>Luz Atlagich González</title><link>/team/luz/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/team/luz/</guid><description>Luz is a medical radiologist who joined the Radiomics Group in 2022. She works as a radiologist in clinical trials and is currently a research fellow in Oncologic Imaging, participating in different projects within the group.</description></item></channel></rss>