<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Publications on Radiomics</title><link>/publications/</link><description>Recent content in Publications on Radiomics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Diffusion MRI signal cumulants and hepatocyte microstructure at fixed diffusion time: Insights from simulations, 9.4T imaging, and histology</title><link>/publications/pub8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/publications/pub8/</guid><description>F Grussu, K Bernatowicz, I Casanova-Salas, N Castro, P Nuciforo, J Mateo, I Barba, R Perez-Lopez. Diffusion MRI signal cumulants and hepatocyte microstructure at fixed diffusion time: Insights from simulations, 9.4T imaging, and histology. Magnetic Resonance in Medicine 88(1): 365-379 (2022); doi: 10.1002/mrm.29174.</description></item><item><title>Robust imaging habitat computation using voxel-wise radiomics features</title><link>/publications/pub1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/publications/pub1/</guid><description>K Bernatowicz, F Grussu, M Ligero, et al., R Perez-Lopez. Robust imaging habitat computation using voxel-wise radiomics features. Scientific Reports 11, 20133(2021); doi:10.1038/s41598-021-99701-2.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Diffusion-Weighted MRI for Cancer Microstructure Assessment in Body Imaging, and Its Relationship With Histology</title><link>/publications/pub10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/publications/pub10/</guid><description>E Fokkinga, J A Hernandez-Tamames, A Ianus, M Nilsson, C M W Tax, R Perez-Lopez*, F Grussu* (* joint corresponding authors and joint senior/last authors). Advanced Diffusion-Weighted MRI for Cancer Microstructure Assessment in Body Imaging, and Its Relationship With Histology. Journal of Magnetic Resonance Imaging (2023, e-pub ahead of print); doi: 10.1002/jmri.29144. Author accepted manuscript available here.</description></item><item><title>The Role of CT-Based Radiomics in Precise Imaging of Renal Cancer</title><link>/publications/pub2-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/publications/pub2-/</guid><description>M Ligero, K Bernatowicz, R Perez-Lopez. The Role of CT-Based Radiomics in Precise Imaging of Renal Cancer. J Nephrol Sci. 2(2), 1-7 (2021); url:https://www.nephrojournal.com2.</description></item><item><title>Voxel-level analysis of normalized DSC-PWI time-intensity curves: a potential generalizable approach and its proof of concept in discriminating glioblastoma and metastasis</title><link>/publications/pub9/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/publications/pub9/</guid><description>A Pons-Escoda, A Garcia-Ruiz, P Naval-Baudin, F Grussu, JJS Fernandez, AC Simo, NV Sarro, A Fernandez-Coello, J Bruna, M Cos, R Perez-Lopez, C Majos. Voxel-level analysis of normalized DSC-PWI time-intensity curves: a potential generalizable approach and its proof of concept in discriminating glioblastoma and metastasis. European Radiology 32, 6, 3705-3715 (2022); doi: 10.1007/s00330-021-08498-1.</description></item><item><title>A CT-based Radiomics Signature Is Associated with Response to Immune Checkpoint Inhibitors in Advanced Solid Tumors</title><link>/publications/pub3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/publications/pub3/</guid><description>M Ligero, A Garcia-Ruiz, C Viaplana, et al., R Perez-Lopez. A CT-based Radiomics Signature Is Associated with Response to Immune Checkpoint Inhibitors in Advanced Solid Tumors. Radiology. Vol 299, No 1 (2021); doi: 10.1148/radiol.2021200928</description></item><item><title>Precise enhancement quantification in post-operative MRI as an indicator of residual tumor impact is associated with survival in patients with glioblastoma.</title><link>/publications/pub4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/publications/pub4/</guid><description>A Garcia-Ruiz, P Naval-Baudin, M Ligero, et al., R Perez-Lopez. Precise enhancement quantification in post-operative MRI as an indicator of residual tumor impact is associated with survival in patients with glioblastoma. Scientific Reports. 11 - 695 (2021); doi: 10.1038/s41598-020-79829-3</description></item><item><title>Minimizing acquisition-related radiomics variability by image resampling and batch effect correction to allow for large-scale data analysis</title><link>/publications/pub5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/publications/pub5/</guid><description>M Ligero, O Jordi-Ollero, K Bernatowicz,et al., R Perez-Lopez. Minimizing acquisition-related radiomics variability by image resampling and batch effect correction to allow for large-scale data analysis. European Radiology. 31, 1460–1470 (2020); doi: 10.1007/s00330-020-07174-0</description></item><item><title>Correlation of the tumour-stroma ratio with diffusion weighted MRI in rectal cancer</title><link>/publications/pub6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/publications/pub6/</guid><description>S M Zunder, R Perez-Lopez, &amp;hellip;, A Garcia-Ruiz, et al. W E Mesker. Correlation of the tumour-stroma ratio with diffusion weighted MRI in rectal cancer. European Journal of Radiology 133, 109345-109345 (2020); doi: 10.1016/j.ejrad.2020.109345</description></item><item><title>Capturing Hyperprogressive disease with immune checkpoint inhibitors using RECIST 1.1 criteria</title><link>/publications/pub7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/publications/pub7/</guid><description>I Matos, &amp;hellip;, A Garcia Ruiz, et al., Perez-Lopez R, Garralda, E. Capturing Hyperprogressive disease with immune checkpoint inhibitors using RECIST 1.1 criteria. Clinical Cancer Research 26, 8, 1846-1855 (2020); ISSN 1078-0432; doi: 10.1158/1078-0432.CCR-19-2226</description></item></channel></rss>